{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215521158","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215521158"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 4d4c7d77-777c-430b-93b8-d9b010f114d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215522121","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215522121"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 4d4c7d77-777c-430b-93b8-d9b010f114d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215525039","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215525039"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 4d4c7d77-777c-430b-93b8-d9b010f114d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNATAKA"," userResponse":" KUNATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215525573","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215525573"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 4d4c7d77-777c-430b-93b8-d9b010f114d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215526216","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215526216"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 4d4c7d77-777c-430b-93b8-d9b010f114d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAONE"," userResponse":" YAONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215530298","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215530298"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 4d4c7d77-777c-430b-93b8-d9b010f114d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASIKIO"," userResponse":" MASIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215531232","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215531232"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 4d4c7d77-777c-430b-93b8-d9b010f114d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIKIE"," userResponse":" YASIKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215534872","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215534872"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 4d4c7d77-777c-430b-93b8-d9b010f114d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215535661","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215535661"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 4d4c7d77-777c-430b-93b8-d9b010f114d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215536635","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215536634"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 4d4c7d77-777c-430b-93b8-d9b010f114d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215540495","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215540494"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 4d4c7d77-777c-430b-93b8-d9b010f114d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215541469","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215541468"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 4d4c7d77-777c-430b-93b8-d9b010f114d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215544376","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215544376"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 4d4c7d77-777c-430b-93b8-d9b010f114d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNATAKA"," userResponse":" KUNATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215544918","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215544918"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 4d4c7d77-777c-430b-93b8-d9b010f114d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215545562","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215545562"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 4d4c7d77-777c-430b-93b8-d9b010f114d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAONE"," userResponse":" YAONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215549705","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215549704"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 4d4c7d77-777c-430b-93b8-d9b010f114d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASIKIO"," userResponse":" MASIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215550632","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215550631"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 4d4c7d77-777c-430b-93b8-d9b010f114d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIKIE"," userResponse":" YASIKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215554299","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215554299"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 4d4c7d77-777c-430b-93b8-d9b010f114d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215555081","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215555081"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 4d4c7d77-777c-430b-93b8-d9b010f114d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215556055","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215556055"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 4d4c7d77-777c-430b-93b8-d9b010f114d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215559337","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215559337"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 4d4c7d77-777c-430b-93b8-d9b010f114d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215559392","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215559392"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 4d4c7d77-777c-430b-93b8-d9b010f114d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215658777","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215658775"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 4d4c7d77-777c-430b-93b8-d9b010f114d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215658877","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215658877"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 57231124-7f85-47d2-a3a2-30f36b9f8f73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215753764","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215753763"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 57231124-7f85-47d2-a3a2-30f36b9f8f73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215753870","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215753870"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 3511ba94-7cab-413a-8281-9e220e8a10fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215768320","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215768320"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 70e64f49-579d-48c7-85e3-46a99570c77a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" IMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMBA"," userResponse":" IMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215772733","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215772733"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 70e64f49-579d-48c7-85e3-46a99570c77a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" IMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMBA"," userResponse":" IMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215774329","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215774328"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 70e64f49-579d-48c7-85e3-46a99570c77a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ILIKI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKI"," userResponse":" ILIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215782442","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215782441"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 70e64f49-579d-48c7-85e3-46a99570c77a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ILIKI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKI"," userResponse":" ILIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215784062","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215784062"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 70e64f49-579d-48c7-85e3-46a99570c77a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" INGIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGIA"," userResponse":" INGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215794731","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215794731"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 70e64f49-579d-48c7-85e3-46a99570c77a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" INGIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215796354","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215796354"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 70e64f49-579d-48c7-85e3-46a99570c77a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" IMEJAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEJAA"," userResponse":" IMEJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215804531","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215804530"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 70e64f49-579d-48c7-85e3-46a99570c77a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" IMEJAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215806565","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215806564"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 70e64f49-579d-48c7-85e3-46a99570c77a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" IMEJAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215806807","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215806807"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 70e64f49-579d-48c7-85e3-46a99570c77a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" IMEJAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.mc.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215817934","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215817934"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" d8af58c4-c028-424f-a981-11fb0eb90375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.mc.21"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_8-9-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.mc.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215824081","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215824080"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" d8af58c4-c028-424f-a981-11fb0eb90375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.mc.21"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_8-9-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.mc.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215830609","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215830609"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" d8af58c4-c028-424f-a981-11fb0eb90375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.mc.21"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_0-1-8"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.mc.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215837735","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215837735"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" d8af58c4-c028-424f-a981-11fb0eb90375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.mc.21"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_6-7-3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.mc.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215843706","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215843705"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" d8af58c4-c028-424f-a981-11fb0eb90375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.mc.21"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_6-7-3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.mc.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215855088","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215855088"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" d8af58c4-c028-424f-a981-11fb0eb90375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.mc.21"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_7-4-6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.mc.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215861464","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215861463"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" d8af58c4-c028-424f-a981-11fb0eb90375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.mc.21"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_4-5-3"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.mc.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215867587","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215867587"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" d8af58c4-c028-424f-a981-11fb0eb90375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.mc.21"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_0-4-9"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.mc.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215873384","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215873384"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" d8af58c4-c028-424f-a981-11fb0eb90375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.mc.21"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_4-1-3"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.mc.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215878371","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215878371"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" d8af58c4-c028-424f-a981-11fb0eb90375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.mc.21"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-8-9"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.mc.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215883628","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215883628"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" d8af58c4-c028-424f-a981-11fb0eb90375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.mc.21"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-4-8"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.mc.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215889062","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215889061"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" d8af58c4-c028-424f-a981-11fb0eb90375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.mc.21"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_7-0-3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.mc.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215895782","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215895781"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" d8af58c4-c028-424f-a981-11fb0eb90375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.mc.21"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_0_7-0-3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:I..I.vow.10.rand.say.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215916722","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215916722"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" b4b60c03-6529-4754-a353-da3dd0ee23dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_I..I.vow.10.rand.say.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_I_O_U"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:I..I.vow.10.rand.say.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215923397","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215923397"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" b4b60c03-6529-4754-a353-da3dd0ee23dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_I..I.vow.10.rand.say.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_E_I_U"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:I..I.vow.10.rand.say.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215930042","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215930042"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" b4b60c03-6529-4754-a353-da3dd0ee23dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_I..I.vow.10.rand.say.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_O_A_I"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:I..I.vow.10.rand.say.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215936729","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215936728"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" b4b60c03-6529-4754-a353-da3dd0ee23dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_I..I.vow.10.rand.say.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_O_E_I"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:I..I.vow.10.rand.say.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215943373","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215943372"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" b4b60c03-6529-4754-a353-da3dd0ee23dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_I..I.vow.10.rand.say.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_E_A_I"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:I..I.vow.10.rand.say.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215950036","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215950035"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" b4b60c03-6529-4754-a353-da3dd0ee23dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_I..I.vow.10.rand.say.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_I_U_O"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:I..I.vow.10.rand.say.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215956711","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215956710"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" b4b60c03-6529-4754-a353-da3dd0ee23dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_I..I.vow.10.rand.say.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_O_U_I"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:I..I.vow.10.rand.say.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215963389","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215963388"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" b4b60c03-6529-4754-a353-da3dd0ee23dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_I..I.vow.10.rand.say.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_U_I_E"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:I..I.vow.10.rand.say.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215970028","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215970027"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" b4b60c03-6529-4754-a353-da3dd0ee23dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_I..I.vow.10.rand.say.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_E_U_I"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:I..I.vow.10.rand.say.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215976678","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215976678"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" b4b60c03-6529-4754-a353-da3dd0ee23dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_I..I.vow.10.rand.say.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_O_U_I"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:I..I.vow.10.rand.say.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215989880","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215989880"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" b4b60c03-6529-4754-a353-da3dd0ee23dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_I..I.vow.10.rand.say.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_O_U_I"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216061520","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216061519"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" b4b60c03-6529-4754-a353-da3dd0ee23dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_I..I.vow.10.rand.say.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_O_U_I"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216061637","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216061637"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" e7bbdd72-ff53-48c7-87fd-8378035a621d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216069764","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216069764"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" e7bbdd72-ff53-48c7-87fd-8378035a621d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216084200","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216084199"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 632a5a28-297a-49ec-b097-f78310ede87d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216086006","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216086006"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 632a5a28-297a-49ec-b097-f78310ede87d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216092558","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216092558"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 632a5a28-297a-49ec-b097-f78310ede87d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216094516","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216094515"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 632a5a28-297a-49ec-b097-f78310ede87d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216101558","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216101557"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 632a5a28-297a-49ec-b097-f78310ede87d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216103363","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216103363"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 632a5a28-297a-49ec-b097-f78310ede87d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216109989","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216109988"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 632a5a28-297a-49ec-b097-f78310ede87d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nne"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216111748","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216111747"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 632a5a28-297a-49ec-b097-f78310ede87d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nne"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" NNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216118471","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216118470"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 632a5a28-297a-49ec-b097-f78310ede87d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216120289","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216120288"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 632a5a28-297a-49ec-b097-f78310ede87d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216126902","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216126902"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 632a5a28-297a-49ec-b097-f78310ede87d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216128850","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216128850"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 632a5a28-297a-49ec-b097-f78310ede87d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216135946","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216135945"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 632a5a28-297a-49ec-b097-f78310ede87d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216137770","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216137769"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 632a5a28-297a-49ec-b097-f78310ede87d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216143879","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216143878"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 632a5a28-297a-49ec-b097-f78310ede87d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nne"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216145648","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216145647"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 632a5a28-297a-49ec-b097-f78310ede87d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nne"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" NNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216147794","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216147793"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 632a5a28-297a-49ec-b097-f78310ede87d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" nne"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216147941","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216147941"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 632a5a28-297a-49ec-b097-f78310ede87d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nne"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" NNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216160457","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216160457"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" ae2233ac-f9f0-46f2-85fa-aec60fe02fcc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216166427","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216166426"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" ae2233ac-f9f0-46f2-85fa-aec60fe02fcc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216168013","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216168013"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" ae2233ac-f9f0-46f2-85fa-aec60fe02fcc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216173513","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216173512"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" ae2233ac-f9f0-46f2-85fa-aec60fe02fcc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216175135","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216175134"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" ae2233ac-f9f0-46f2-85fa-aec60fe02fcc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216175391","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216175390"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" ae2233ac-f9f0-46f2-85fa-aec60fe02fcc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216175484","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216175484"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" ae2233ac-f9f0-46f2-85fa-aec60fe02fcc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216215559","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216215558"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" ae2233ac-f9f0-46f2-85fa-aec60fe02fcc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216215622","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216215622"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 67301992-004a-4544-8932-5ee212f97689"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" KIMYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.21__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216225254","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216225254"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 13f5ea06-25d1-4b1f-a6ff-c7916bbd8868"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.21__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_I-U-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.21__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216229238","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216229238"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 13f5ea06-25d1-4b1f-a6ff-c7916bbd8868"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.21__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_E-A-O"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.21__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216233114","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216233114"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 13f5ea06-25d1-4b1f-a6ff-c7916bbd8868"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.21__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_I-A-U"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.21__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216236821","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216236821"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 13f5ea06-25d1-4b1f-a6ff-c7916bbd8868"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.21__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_E-O-A"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.21__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216240570","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216240570"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 13f5ea06-25d1-4b1f-a6ff-c7916bbd8868"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.21__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_A-U-I"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.21__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216246326","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216246321"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 13f5ea06-25d1-4b1f-a6ff-c7916bbd8868"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.21__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_U_A-U-I"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.rise.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216260247","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216260247"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" cf446ddc-d0ee-4448-b400-05936281cde5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.rise.22"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_6-3-9"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.rise.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216266325","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216266325"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" cf446ddc-d0ee-4448-b400-05936281cde5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.rise.22"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-9-5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.rise.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216272157","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216272157"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" cf446ddc-d0ee-4448-b400-05936281cde5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.rise.22"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-9-5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.rise.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216279388","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216279388"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" cf446ddc-d0ee-4448-b400-05936281cde5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.rise.22"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_0-7-6"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.rise.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216284908","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216284908"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" cf446ddc-d0ee-4448-b400-05936281cde5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.rise.22"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_0-7-6"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.rise.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216292451","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216292451"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" cf446ddc-d0ee-4448-b400-05936281cde5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.rise.22"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_8-7-6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.rise.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216299740","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216299740"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" cf446ddc-d0ee-4448-b400-05936281cde5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.rise.22"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_8-7-6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.rise.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216307891","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216307891"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" cf446ddc-d0ee-4448-b400-05936281cde5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.rise.22"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-7-2"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.rise.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216314020","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216314020"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" cf446ddc-d0ee-4448-b400-05936281cde5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.rise.22"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_8-9-4"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.rise.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216320384","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216320384"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" cf446ddc-d0ee-4448-b400-05936281cde5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.rise.22"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_7-0-3"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.rise.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216325898","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216325898"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" cf446ddc-d0ee-4448-b400-05936281cde5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.rise.22"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_9-2-7"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.rise.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216332170","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216332170"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" cf446ddc-d0ee-4448-b400-05936281cde5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.rise.22"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_6-0-1"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.rise.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216337708","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216337708"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" cf446ddc-d0ee-4448-b400-05936281cde5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.rise.22"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_4-0-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.rise.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216344433","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216344432"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" cf446ddc-d0ee-4448-b400-05936281cde5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.rise.22"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_0_4-0-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.22__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216437285","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216437285"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" cf446ddc-d0ee-4448-b400-05936281cde5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.rise.22"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_0_4-0-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216465674","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216465674"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 0e57b0ec-ee78-4f29-8e6e-c934fc72c056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216485645","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216485645"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 0e57b0ec-ee78-4f29-8e6e-c934fc72c056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216506170","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216506169"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 0e57b0ec-ee78-4f29-8e6e-c934fc72c056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216508993","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216508992"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 0e57b0ec-ee78-4f29-8e6e-c934fc72c056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216512042","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216512042"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 0e57b0ec-ee78-4f29-8e6e-c934fc72c056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216532080","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216532080"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 0e57b0ec-ee78-4f29-8e6e-c934fc72c056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216553992","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216553992"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 0e57b0ec-ee78-4f29-8e6e-c934fc72c056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216556698","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216556698"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 0e57b0ec-ee78-4f29-8e6e-c934fc72c056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216559579","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216559579"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 0e57b0ec-ee78-4f29-8e6e-c934fc72c056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216574799","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216574797"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 0e57b0ec-ee78-4f29-8e6e-c934fc72c056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216574889","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216574889"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 0e57b0ec-ee78-4f29-8e6e-c934fc72c056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216587131","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216587130"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" e2d36a6b-2154-4bee-b5ac-313c160f4387"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OVAROLI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVAROLI"," userResponse":" OVAROLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216594948","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216594948"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" e2d36a6b-2154-4bee-b5ac-313c160f4387"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OVAROLI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVAROLI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216596561","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216596561"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" e2d36a6b-2154-4bee-b5ac-313c160f4387"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ONA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ONA"," userResponse":" ONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216605830","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216605829"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" e2d36a6b-2154-4bee-b5ac-313c160f4387"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ONA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216607452","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216607452"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" e2d36a6b-2154-4bee-b5ac-313c160f4387"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OFISI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OFISI"," userResponse":" OFISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216614040","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216614039"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" e2d36a6b-2154-4bee-b5ac-313c160f4387"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OFISI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OFISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216615642","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216615642"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" e2d36a6b-2154-4bee-b5ac-313c160f4387"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OGELEA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216620720","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216620720"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" e2d36a6b-2154-4bee-b5ac-313c160f4387"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OGELEA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216622277","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216622276"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" e2d36a6b-2154-4bee-b5ac-313c160f4387"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OSHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OSHA"," userResponse":" OSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216627009","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216627008"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" e2d36a6b-2154-4bee-b5ac-313c160f4387"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OSHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OSHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216628630","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216628629"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" e2d36a6b-2154-4bee-b5ac-313c160f4387"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBA"," userResponse":" OMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216633227","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216633227"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" e2d36a6b-2154-4bee-b5ac-313c160f4387"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216634837","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216634837"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" e2d36a6b-2154-4bee-b5ac-313c160f4387"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OA"," userResponse":" OA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216639935","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216639934"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" e2d36a6b-2154-4bee-b5ac-313c160f4387"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216641957","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216641956"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" e2d36a6b-2154-4bee-b5ac-313c160f4387"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" OA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216642124","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216642124"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" e2d36a6b-2154-4bee-b5ac-313c160f4387"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.rise.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216649868","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216649868"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" e2d36a6b-2154-4bee-b5ac-313c160f4387"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" OA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216660394","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216660394"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" e2d36a6b-2154-4bee-b5ac-313c160f4387"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" OA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216689090","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216689090"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 1f4327eb-bd37-4465-82c3-0a42aaa583ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216712468","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216712468"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 1f4327eb-bd37-4465-82c3-0a42aaa583ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216739376","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216739376"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 1f4327eb-bd37-4465-82c3-0a42aaa583ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216743310","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216743310"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 1f4327eb-bd37-4465-82c3-0a42aaa583ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216762874","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216762873"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 1f4327eb-bd37-4465-82c3-0a42aaa583ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216763026","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216763026"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 1f4327eb-bd37-4465-82c3-0a42aaa583ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:O..O.vow.10.rand.say.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216783715","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216783715"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 6a687f3e-24d3-4588-875f-1305add08cdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_O..O.vow.10.rand.say.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_A_O_I"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:O..O.vow.10.rand.say.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216790422","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216790422"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 6a687f3e-24d3-4588-875f-1305add08cdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_O..O.vow.10.rand.say.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_U_O_A"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:O..O.vow.10.rand.say.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216797068","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216797067"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 6a687f3e-24d3-4588-875f-1305add08cdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_O..O.vow.10.rand.say.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_E_A_O"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:O..O.vow.10.rand.say.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216803707","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216803706"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 6a687f3e-24d3-4588-875f-1305add08cdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_O..O.vow.10.rand.say.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_O_U_I"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:O..O.vow.10.rand.say.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216810370","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216810370"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 6a687f3e-24d3-4588-875f-1305add08cdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_O..O.vow.10.rand.say.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_A_U_O"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:O..O.vow.10.rand.say.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216817069","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216817069"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 6a687f3e-24d3-4588-875f-1305add08cdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_O..O.vow.10.rand.say.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_O_I_U"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:O..O.vow.10.rand.say.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216823730","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216823730"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 6a687f3e-24d3-4588-875f-1305add08cdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_O..O.vow.10.rand.say.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_E_O_I"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:O..O.vow.10.rand.say.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216830363","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216830362"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 6a687f3e-24d3-4588-875f-1305add08cdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_O..O.vow.10.rand.say.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_U_O_A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:O..O.vow.10.rand.say.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216837025","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216837025"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 6a687f3e-24d3-4588-875f-1305add08cdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_O..O.vow.10.rand.say.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_E_O_I"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:O..O.vow.10.rand.say.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216843690","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216843690"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 6a687f3e-24d3-4588-875f-1305add08cdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_O..O.vow.10.rand.say.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_O_A_U"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:O..O.vow.10.rand.say.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216856755","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216856755"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 6a687f3e-24d3-4588-875f-1305add08cdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_O..O.vow.10.rand.say.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_O_A_U"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216870045","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216870044"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" e00c0700-ee10-4cb5-9f58-36817cc48ecf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.7__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sifuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIFURI"," userResponse":" SIFURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216874625","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216874624"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" e00c0700-ee10-4cb5-9f58-36817cc48ecf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.7__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sifuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIFURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216876859","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216876859"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" e00c0700-ee10-4cb5-9f58-36817cc48ecf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.7__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" sifuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216876958","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216876958"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" e00c0700-ee10-4cb5-9f58-36817cc48ecf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.7__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sifuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIFURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216888302","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216888301"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" ae922669-d196-4310-8eca-d69c1c103f10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216888699","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216888699"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" ae922669-d196-4310-8eca-d69c1c103f10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216888944","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216888944"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" ae922669-d196-4310-8eca-d69c1c103f10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216889265","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216889264"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" ae922669-d196-4310-8eca-d69c1c103f10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216889506","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216889505"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" ae922669-d196-4310-8eca-d69c1c103f10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216892984","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216892983"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" ae922669-d196-4310-8eca-d69c1c103f10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216893283","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216893282"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" ae922669-d196-4310-8eca-d69c1c103f10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216894189","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216894188"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" ae922669-d196-4310-8eca-d69c1c103f10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216894620","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216894619"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" ae922669-d196-4310-8eca-d69c1c103f10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216897628","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216897624"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" ae922669-d196-4310-8eca-d69c1c103f10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216897923","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216897923"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" ae922669-d196-4310-8eca-d69c1c103f10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216898772","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216898772"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" ae922669-d196-4310-8eca-d69c1c103f10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216899451","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216899451"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" ae922669-d196-4310-8eca-d69c1c103f10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216900199","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216900198"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" ae922669-d196-4310-8eca-d69c1c103f10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216900534","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216900532"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" ae922669-d196-4310-8eca-d69c1c103f10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216900820","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216900820"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" ae922669-d196-4310-8eca-d69c1c103f10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216901144","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216901144"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" ae922669-d196-4310-8eca-d69c1c103f10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216901421","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216901421"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" ae922669-d196-4310-8eca-d69c1c103f10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216903623","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216903623"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" ae922669-d196-4310-8eca-d69c1c103f10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216903698","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216903698"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" ae922669-d196-4310-8eca-d69c1c103f10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216936966","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216936965"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" ffd79b2e-ce12-4c51-9e7b-0b3541eb0108"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kimya_vya-chako-kimya-tamu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kimya"," userResponse":" kimya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216959304","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216959303"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" ffd79b2e-ce12-4c51-9e7b-0b3541eb0108"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" kimya_vya-chako-kimya-tamu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216959399","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216959399"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" ffd79b2e-ce12-4c51-9e7b-0b3541eb0108"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216966960","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216966960"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" ffd79b2e-ce12-4c51-9e7b-0b3541eb0108"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216975535","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216975534"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" ffd79b2e-ce12-4c51-9e7b-0b3541eb0108"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.21__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549216985523","data":{"timestamp":" 1549216985523"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" ffd79b2e-ce12-4c51-9e7b-0b3541eb0108"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549217015020","data":{"timestamp":" 1549217015019"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 210c9652-dc92-47ee-b9bb-ad56524d95c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" njaa_ambayo-shule-njaa-hadithi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" njaa"," userResponse":" njaa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549217037968","data":{"timestamp":" 1549217037967"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 210c9652-dc92-47ee-b9bb-ad56524d95c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yake_tena-kisha-kuwa-yake"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" yake"," userResponse":" yake"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549217075901","data":{"timestamp":" 1549217075901"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 210c9652-dc92-47ee-b9bb-ad56524d95c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kichekesho_kichekesho-madirisha-ukatili-pumua"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kichekesho"," userResponse":" kichekesho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549217101161","data":{"timestamp":" 1549217101161"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 210c9652-dc92-47ee-b9bb-ad56524d95c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kimya_kuna-kuliko-kimya-tamu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kimya"," userResponse":" kimya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549217121050","data":{"timestamp":" 1549217121050"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 210c9652-dc92-47ee-b9bb-ad56524d95c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nini_nini-katika-mamba-moto"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nini"," userResponse":" nini"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549217129967","data":{"timestamp":" 1549217129966"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 210c9652-dc92-47ee-b9bb-ad56524d95c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" nini_nini-katika-mamba-moto"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549217130077","data":{"timestamp":" 1549217130077"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 210c9652-dc92-47ee-b9bb-ad56524d95c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.uc.2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549217139397","data":{"timestamp":" 1549217139397"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 210c9652-dc92-47ee-b9bb-ad56524d95c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549217149399","data":{"timestamp":" 1549217149399"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 210c9652-dc92-47ee-b9bb-ad56524d95c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.22__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549217158331","data":{"timestamp":" 1549217158331"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 210c9652-dc92-47ee-b9bb-ad56524d95c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549217186192","data":{"timestamp":" 1549217186192"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" 210c9652-dc92-47ee-b9bb-ad56524d95c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549217186263","data":{"timestamp":" 1549217186263"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_203820"," gameId":" cc550013-66fa-4a04-9f1d-d9ca71fb2559"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}